https://www.agricover.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
This is Agricover.com's ("Agricover.com") online privacy policy ("Policy"). This policy applies only to activities Agricover.com engages in on its website and does not apply to Agricover.com activities "offline" or unrelated to the website.
INFORMATION GATHERED BY AGRICOVER.COM
Agricover.com collects certain anonymous data regarding the usage of the website. This information does not personally identify users, by itself or in combination with other information, and is gathered to improve the performance of the website. The anonymous data collected by the Agricover.com website can include information such as the type of browser you are using, browsing patterns, originating web pages, number of visits to Agricover.com, vehicle selections, items viewed, pages viewed and the length of the visit to the website.
You may also be asked to provide personally identifiable information on the Agricover.com website, which may include your name, address, telephone number
and e-mail address. In addition, if a purchase is made, we collect credit card information, billing and shipping address, customer information, vehicle information and prior purchases. This information can be gathered when feedback or e-mails are sent to Agricover.com, when you register for services, or make purchases via the website. In all such cases you have the option of providing us with personally identifiable information. You may always choose not to provide the requested information, but you then may not be able to participate in the particular activity that requires such information. If you do provide us with your personally identifiable information, you agree we may contact you to provide you with information we believe may be of interest to you.
COOKIES
We use cookies to track certain browsing patterns on the website. Cookies are small bits of data cached in a user's browser. Agricover.com utilizes cookies to personalize your experience on Agricover.com, assist you in using Agricover.com and allow us to compile site usage statistics to better improve our goods, services and products. Cookies may also be used to conduct marketing and promotional efforts, tailor advertisements to your browser or determine the popularity of our content. The cookies collect certain identifying information, including customer identifiers generated by us, as well as a visitor ID that will, in certain circumstances, be matched with personally identifiable information. However, no other user information is gathered by cookies.
USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
Except as otherwise stated below, we do not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information collected on the site to others. The information collected by our site is used to confirm and process orders, to keep you informed about your order status, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you, to obtain reviews, ratings or testimonials relating to your experience with Agricover products purchased and for statistical purposes for improving our site. We will disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for tracking purposes, to charge your credit card (or process your check or money order, as appropriate), fill your order, improve the functionality of our site, perform statistical and data analyses, deliver your order and deliver promotional emails to you from us. For example, we must release your credit card number to confirm payment and release your mailing address information to the delivery service to deliver products you ordered.
Agricover.com may use non-personal "aggregated data" to enhance the operation of our website or analyze interest in the areas of our website. Moreover, we may in some circumstances disclose personally identifiable information to third parties to enhance your experience on our website. Additionally, if you provide Agricover.com with content for publishing or feedback, we may publish your user name or other identifying data.
Agricover.com may also disclose personally identifiable information in order to respond to a subpoena, court order or other such request. Agricover.com may also provide such personally identifiable information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or as otherwise required by law. Your personally identifiable information may be provided to a party if Agricover.com files for bankruptcy or there is a transfer of the assets or ownership of Agricover.com in connection with proposed or consummated corporate reorganizations, such as mergers or acquisitions
SECURITY
Agricover.com takes appropriate steps to ensure data privacy and security through various hardware and software methodologies. Your transaction is secure in that you would pay nothing in the event an unauthorized charge was made to your credit card after purchasing from Agricover. However, Agricover.com cannot guarantee the security of any information disclosed online.
877-708-4787
3000 Hwy 281 SE
Jamestown, ND, 58401
Monday - Friday
7:30am - 5:00pm (CST)
© 2020 Agri-Cover, Inc. Manufacturer reserves the right to make changes at any time. Patents Information  Privacy Policy
© 2020 Agri-Cover, Inc. Manufacturer reserves the right to make changes at any time.Patents Information      Privacy Policy
